Jessica Weber

(626) 695-7017 hello@jessicaweber.io www.jessicaweber.io Los Angeles, CA

CAREER

Freelance Web Developer — Web Developer

NOVEMBER 2017 - CURRENT

- Initial set up, hosting and domain for a ministry and customized a Squarespace theme with CSS & HTML
- Website rebuild and migration from Wix to WordPress for a nonprofit organization
- Ongoing maintenance for a ministry and nonprofit organization
 - Updating plugins, backing up databases and adding any feature requests

goop, Santa Monica, CA — Web Producer (CMS, Wordpress)

MAY 2018 - NOVEMBER 2018

- Developed WordPress and Spree web pages based on PSD designs using HTML & CSS, JavaScript & JQuery
- Contributed to a company codebase while maintaining clean & clear coding standards
- Collaborated with Ad Sales, Design, Product and UX teams to reach maximum audience and partnership opportunities

OUTREACH

Lean In Los Angeles, Los Angeles, CA — Website Manager

SEPTEMBER 2018 - CURRENT

- Manage and maintain website with up to date chapter activities
- Proactively contribute ideas for website improvement
- Collaborate with team to generate content for website and blog to drive more traffic

Athena.LA, Los Angeles, CA — Community Manager

NOVEMBER 2017 - CURRENT

Attend tech networking events & workshops to connect with potential speakers and promote Athena.LA to increase female and minority representation within S.T.E.M. fields

EDUCATION

Western Washington University, Bellingham, WA

MARCH 2012

© B.A. in Spanish Language and Minor in Business Administration

PROFESSIONAL STATEMENT

Proactive and intellectually curious with the desire and capability to learn new technologies, languages and frameworks. Has experience editing and updating existing websites and dynamic web applications. Builds close working relationships with teammates and collaborates to find effective solutions. Effectively executes procedures to improve internal processes. Focused and organized; ready to take on a challenge. A passionate team player who strives to positively contribute to overall company goals.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- ▽ HTML & CSS, PHP7,

 Javascript, JQuery
- Wordpress, Wix,SquareSpace
- Version Control (Git), MAMP, phpMyAdmin
- ♡ Photoshop, Sketch
- WPEngine, HostGator, GoDaddy